<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Aboot Town</title>
 <link href="http://aboottown.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://aboottown.com/"/>
 <updated>2015-11-27T19:18:35-07:00</updated>
 <id>http://aboottown.com</id>
 <author>
   <name>Adam Wooster</name>
   <email>adamblog@gmail.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>First Princess Day</title>
   <link href="http://aboottown.com/2015/11/25/First-Princess-Day/"/>
   <updated>2015-11-25T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://aboottown.com/2015/11/25/First-Princess-Day</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h1 id='the_first_princess_day_or_how_i_learned_that_mexican_amateur_porn_involving_bicycles_is_just_better'&gt;The First Princess Day: or How I Learned that Mexican Amateur Porn Involving Bicycles is Just Better&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sitting here, eating a fresh egg-salad&lt;sup id='fnref:1'&gt;&lt;a href='#fn:1' rel='footnote'&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; with corn chips and sipping some tequila, I am comforted by the comfortable distance of a few days between the writing of this post, and the actual events being recorded. I had several visceral physical reactions to my first princess day outing, and they left me questioning many things&lt;sup id='fnref:2'&gt;&lt;a href='#fn:2' rel='footnote'&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, our story begins much earlier where, flush from the triumphant baptism of a new day&lt;sup id='fnref:3'&gt;&lt;a href='#fn:3' rel='footnote'&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;, I and several other friends decided to inaugurate princess day. After considering the listings of events in Boulder, I found one that seemed quirky, original, and obscure enough to mark one as a man who had his finger on the pulse of the city. Perfect date material, even if the date is oneself. This is how I decided on Bike Smut! A Film Festival dedicated to exploring the intersection of mobility and sexuality&lt;sup id='fnref:4'&gt;&lt;a href='#fn:4' rel='footnote'&gt;4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. This would then be followed by One Dollar Tacos at Mountain Sun. A one-two combination sure to dazzle anyone! Tacos, then tacos&lt;sup id='fnref:5'&gt;&lt;a href='#fn:5' rel='footnote'&gt;5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plus, as an avowed Star Trek, Star Wars and all around science fiction fan, the added cherry on top was that this year the theme was Science Friction. All this was to turn to ash in my mouth. The eating-tacos at the Mountain Sun were nice though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id='the_festival'&gt;The Festival.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, a disclaimer. Please read the below as one man trying to put you in his, admittedly purityrannical, reaction to these films. My comments are not meant to be body-shaming &lt;sup id='fnref:6'&gt;&lt;a href='#fn:6' rel='footnote'&gt;6&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; in anyway&amp;#8211; I am merely trying to describe the intense reactions that I felt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mexican Lesbians. They kiss, one goes riding, one starts masturbating. Commentary on the solo, fetishized &amp;#8216;movement-for-movement&amp;#8217;s-sake&amp;#8217; philosophy of recreational cycling? Perhaps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Charlie Chaplin. Begins in black and white. Homeless man gifts sex toy to woman. She uses it (offscreen&lt;sup id='fnref:7'&gt;&lt;a href='#fn:7' rel='footnote'&gt;7&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;), and the world becomes full of vibrant colours.&lt;sup id='fnref:8'&gt;&lt;a href='#fn:8' rel='footnote'&gt;8&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hispanic woman masturbates while straddling bicycle in a park. Most &amp;#8216;arty&amp;#8217; of the films. I enjoyed this for its tasteful restraint. By using metaphorical imagery (notably, an engorged red balloon inflating), and accompanied by a dulcimer that discordantly hammered away, the audience was induced into an anxious, uncomfortable, but aroused state. Presumably the same state that would lead a Mexican to masturbate on a bike in a park.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shitty &amp;#8216;arty&amp;#8217; film&amp;#8211;German Neo Expressionism taken so seriously it becomes parody. Derivative.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Note. At this point, I had begun pulling from a flask that I had secreted on my person, and things start to become a little hazy.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;?. Domestic mystery, detective noire. Bikes are sentient. One enlists the aid of a hardboiled detective to unravel domestic affair. Detective peaks in on couple having sex while standing over a bike. Note: this is the first real &amp;#8216;porn&amp;#8217;, in the sex scene has no artistic merit and is just two people fucking with bad sound production. And lots of hair.&lt;sup id='fnref:9'&gt;&lt;a href='#fn:9' rel='footnote'&gt;9&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;?+1. Post-apocalyptic. Woman tracks down man, brainwashes him into having sex with her&lt;sup id='fnref:10'&gt;&lt;a href='#fn:10' rel='footnote'&gt;10&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; First close up of a dick and cum-on-titties-shot. Dick has an interesting geometry. Also, I realized that when men walk with hard dicks it looks like Jim Hennison is controlling it somewhere offscreen, giving it an alien rythmn as it bobs and weaves. This film was silent, and better for it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;?+2. Bike sleeps around. Best filmed straight-up porn scene. Good lighting, music was suitable. Also Mexican&amp;#8211; no surprise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;?+3. Post-apocalyptic with heavy handed morality segues into weird glitter sex with &amp;#8216;Rubenesque&amp;#8217; girl.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;?+4. Animated. (Also, no surprise, Mexican.) Artistic, fun. Highlight of the festival.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;?+5. &amp;#8216;Classic&amp;#8217; style porn with two sex scenes. One where a drugged man is anally penetrated with a strapon. Again, I am triggered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By far the worst of the night was a prolonged skit where one of the presenters dressed up like Picard, and then fought Khan, to the music where Kirk fights Spock when Spock has succumbed to the anicient Vulcan mating drive known as Pon Farr in the &amp;#8220;Amok Time&amp;#8221; espisode of the Orginal Series. It hurt to watch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then Darth Vader entered the scene and while I didn&amp;#8217;t gag this time, I felt an intense feeling of disgust. Not merely content to rape drugged up black dudes, the Bike Smut festival had now violated some of the most sacred science fiction icons of our time. I was greatly disappointed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, we left, and went to get tacos. And we thought about what just happened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id='closing_thoughts'&gt;Closing thoughts.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Somewhere in there was a film that caused a physical reaction from me. Two lesbians, one young, one old, have sex in a bike shop. The older one is hoisted up, so she is suspended in mid-air. A Macgyvered sex-toy in the form of a screwdriver whose shaft had been driven into a drill, and all covered with a condom is brought up to her vagina.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, something about the combination of a moist, hairy, and meaty&lt;sup id='fnref:11'&gt;&lt;a href='#fn:11' rel='footnote'&gt;11&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; vagina being perturbed by a screwdriver handle moving at 100 rpm made me gag. Seeing the vagina undulate like the Baron Harkonnen smacking his lips, hearing the tinny whine of the power drill, seeing the light glisten off her labia like roast beef under the buffet heat lamps, and the almost surgical dispassion of the young woman operating the drill, it all combined to produce a sensory experience that was overwhelming to me, and I gagged. Repeatedly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am still coming to terms with: a) my reaction to that, and b) what that says about me. Have I been so indoctrinated by media and well-produced porn to only find hairless (or tasteful landing stripped), vaginas whose cup does not overflowth with meat, attractive?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes. I suppose so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fucking patriarchy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the words of Supreme Court Justice Potter when asked how to distinguish good porn from bad porn&amp;#8211; &amp;#8220;I know it when I see it&amp;#8221;, and unfortunately, that night I didn&amp;#8217;t see any.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class='footnotes'&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li id='fn:1'&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Soooo fucking fresh&lt;sup id='fnref:12'&gt;&lt;a href='#fn:12' rel='footnote'&gt;12&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href='#fnref:1' rev='footnote'&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id='fn:2'&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vaginas? Hair? Naturalness: Is it Beautiful?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href='#fnref:2' rev='footnote'&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id='fn:3'&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Frequent readers of my blog will know that it gives me pleasure to baptise a new day, ie. Bitch Day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href='#fnref:3' rev='footnote'&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id='fn:4'&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, a refreshing &amp;#8216;sex-positive but also winky innuendo&amp;#8217; vibe that would be sure to score points with a woman who belongs in 2015.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href='#fnref:4' rev='footnote'&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id='fn:5'&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#8217;m sorry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href='#fnref:5' rev='footnote'&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id='fn:6'&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although, where do you drawn the line? No one is telling people with inflamed buttholes to be proud of them. There are no butthole movement on twitter where people post pictures of their buttholes and are congratulated on having a beautiful butthole. But, hairy, meaty vaginas are something to be embraced. I&amp;#8217;m sorry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href='#fnref:6' rev='footnote'&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id='fn:7'&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A rare display of tastefulness from a porn festival.&lt;sup id='fnref:13'&gt;&lt;a href='#fn:13' rel='footnote'&gt;13&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href='#fnref:7' rev='footnote'&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id='fn:8'&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, the reversal of this film technique was used to similarly stunning fashion with the Girl in The Red Coat in Schindler&amp;#8217;s List.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href='#fnref:8' rev='footnote'&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id='fn:9'&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am pro-GMO, and as such, reject the conflation of Naturalness and Beauty. If Michael Jordan shaves his armpits, so can you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href='#fnref:9' rev='footnote'&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id='fn:10'&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gone were my illusions of consent-positivity&lt;sup id='fnref:14'&gt;&lt;a href='#fn:14' rel='footnote'&gt;14&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; in this festival of pornographers. Frequent readers of my blog will suspect that it is here I began to be triggered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href='#fnref:10' rev='footnote'&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id='fn:11'&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like an Arby&amp;#8217;s commercial.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href='#fnref:11' rev='footnote'&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id='fn:12'&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The small, unintended pleasures of bachelor living.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href='#fnref:12' rev='footnote'&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id='fn:13'&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Make no mistake, at this point all notions of a Tasteful Burlesque Show of innuendo and sex-positivity were gone. I was watching pornography. With friends. In a bar. And the sound production was terrible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href='#fnref:13' rev='footnote'&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id='fn:14'&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although, it does raise interesting questions of consent. How would I have felt if the genders were reversed? (even ickier) If it happened over the course of a week and she just manipulated (was charming) him into having sex with her would I feel icky then? (no).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href='#fnref:14' rev='footnote'&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Princess Day</title>
   <link href="http://aboottown.com/2015/11/24/Princess-Day/"/>
   <updated>2015-11-24T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://aboottown.com/2015/11/24/Princess-Day</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Princess day was born out of my frustration with the courtship process. I found that I was spending money, time and energy planning and executing first, second and third dates for complete strangers. Unfortunately, the patriarchy won&amp;#8217;t let women plan and execute their own dates and this asymmetry had started to bother me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Especially with the statistic fact that 50% of the people you meet are going to be &lt;a href='https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Statistics'&gt;shitheads&lt;/a&gt;, this can all add up to heartbreak and dissatisfaction. Thus, Princess Day was born of the simple realization that, instead of treating these complete strangers as princesses to be pampered and feted, I should be treating myself that way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, Princess Day is a date that I take myself, and any close friends who want to come, on. Because, at the end of the day, you are the most important person, so let yourself know that.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Introducing Aboottown</title>
   <link href="http://aboottown.com/2015/11/23/Introducing-aboottown/"/>
   <updated>2015-11-23T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://aboottown.com/2015/11/23/Introducing-aboottown</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h1 id='introduction'&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This blog is for personal use only. Please stop reading immediatly. Its purpose is to record the goings on of a young, single man in Boulder, Colorado.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I created this blog by using this helpful young man&amp;#8217;s &lt;a href='http://joshualande.com/jekyll-github-pages-poole/'&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
