<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Aboot Town</title>
 <link href="http://aboottown.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://aboottown.com/"/>
 <updated>2015-12-03T18:20:44-07:00</updated>
 <id>http://aboottown.com</id>
 <author>
   <name>Adam Wooster</name>
   <email>adamblog@gmail.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Death?</title>
   <link href="http://aboottown.com/2015/11/27/Death%3F/"/>
   <updated>2015-11-27T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://aboottown.com/2015/11/27/Death?</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h1 id='death'&gt;Death?&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8220;Oh! I am so, so sorry!.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is what Tim Keller wanted to say. In fact, he was straining desperately to speak at all. Normally Tim was a very verbose man; in fact, on several occasions he&amp;#8217;d witnessed a conversational partner&amp;#8217;s eyes glaze over. At this point in time, Tim could not voice his thoughts. This was because Tim Keller was drowning and his mouth was full of water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The shame he felt at the thought of having to be rescued was quickly being replaced by full on panic as his head bobbed up and down in the gentle waves. It was an unfortunate turn of events, until this point it had been a very ordinary, but pleasant vacation. The break from work had been welcome, and he had just begun to relax into the trip. A harmless little swim to shed some nervous energy, to just float in the lake and bathe in the sun&amp;#8217;s rays. He could still see his wife and son, splashing in the shallows. His son&amp;#8217;s giggle carried easily over the flat surface of the lake and Tim smiled, despite himself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He was pulled under again, but found he didn&amp;#8217;t have the strength to kick back up. His felt like he was pulling himself through molasses, a sticky morass that clung to him, dragged and clutched, pulling him down, down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This would tear them apart, he thought in a brief moment of lucidity. He could see his son splashing around in those vivid red water wings, while his wife laughed and smiled, her golden hair spinning the sunlight into a halo around her head. At the time, those waterwings had seemed like a harmless, vaguely unmanly, indulgence of the fears of childhood. Now, they seemed like a really good fucking idea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He resurfaced, gasping for breathe. His mouth barely breaching the surface as it sucked and gasped at the air. Recalling a news program he had watched about what to do in the event of drowning, Tim kicked his shoes off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It had been hard for Tim to accept that he was drowning. Even now, he hardly exhibited the symptoms of a drowning man. No cries for help. No dramatic shouts, or splashing. He wasn&amp;#8217;t waving his arms wildly in the air. In fact, Tim seemed altogether too calm for a man drowning. But far from possessing a quiet dignity about the whole thing, this was because Tim had by now inhaled far too much of the waters of Lake Michigan, and was rather tired.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tim clawed at the water, his body fully in the thrall of the brutal, unrelenting motions of panic. With a last burst of strength he forced his head above water. His son, his wife, splashing happily in the shallows. The young lifeguard perched in his tower, leaning down to talk to a young woman in a bikini. Turning his head, he caught Tim&amp;#8217;s eyes. The last thing Tim saw before he went down for the last time was the whites of those eyes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He held his breath. He hadn&amp;#8217;t managed to get much air, and he could feel the clastrophoic pressure of having no air in your lungs, the body screaming, begging for oxygen. It pushed in on him from all sides, from inside of him. He opened his mouth, gagging at the effort require not to breath in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tim looked upwards, he could see the surface, just above his slowly flailing hands. It had the placid dapple of a swimming pool being stirred gently in a summer breeze.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tim breathed out, and then he breathed in. The water rushed in over his eyes, filling his mouth, his nostrils. It was forcing its way into him, pushing into his body. He tried to push, to push it out, but it kept rushing back in, flooding into his spasming lungs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tim had recently watched a nature documentary centered around a pack of Alaskan wolves. One scene in particular had always stuck with him. It was near the end of a chase, the pack had seperated a young deer from its mother and had been herding it, nipping its heels to drive it into exhaustion. The deer was tired of running, you could see it in the whites of its eyes, the way it stumbled and staggered onwards. The wolves had dispensed with pretense and begun to eat it. Tearing steaming chunks out of the deer as it ran and stumbled. The barbarity had shocked Tim at the time, but what had really stuck with him was when, near the end of its run it had just layed down. It was so calm. It had this quiet dignity as it lay there. It didn&amp;#8217;t fight, didn&amp;#8217;t struggle as the wolves ate it alive, picking flesh off its still breathing form. That quiet acceptance had terrified Tim.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tim had stopped struggling now. His lungs still seized, spasming around the fluid rushing to fill them, but he was strangely distant from it. He began to sink, his clothes weighed down by the water. There was a calmness that gripped Tim, and as he watched the last of the air bubble up away from him, he considered that it was probably shock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The last thing Tim felt before he blacked out was a strong hand gripping his hair.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-&amp;gt;*&amp;lt;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A big face, with an angry pimple on its nose. A sparse forest of hairs on the upper lip, and a thin roapy chain of saliva between the upper and lower lip. All of this was swooping down towards Tim in an inevitable slow motion. This was the first thing he saw when he came to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second thing Tim saw was the large crowd of people clustering around him, everone&amp;#8217;s eyes wide, staring directly at him. Tim became more and more aware of the cold, wet feeling of his swim trucks clinging to his thighs. He imagined what he must look like: a middle aged man, muffin topping over his slightly too tight shorts, skinny pale legs lying limply in the sand. All of this caused a deep sense of embarrassment to fall over him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All at once, Tim wished he was back out in the ocean. He tried to say, &amp;#8220;No! Please! I&amp;#8217;m so sorry, I didn&amp;#8217;t mean to be an inconvenience. Really, I&amp;#8217;m fine.&amp;#8221; but his throat had ceased to work. In that moment, Tim truly wanted to die. Instead, he just closed his eyes and did his best to shut out the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tim had been strapped into a stretched and bundled into an ambulance. They hadn&amp;#8217;t shut the doors, and he could hear voices directly outside. &amp;#8220;I don&amp;#8217;t understand it,&amp;#8221; the lifeguard was saying to an EMT, &amp;#8220;maybe I just wasn&amp;#8217;t fast enough&amp;#8230;&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8220;You did your best, okay? This isn&amp;#8217;t anyone&amp;#8217;s fault.&amp;#8221; The EMT paused. &amp;#8220;I just need to ask you, one last time: Did he ever show any signs of responsiveness?&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8220;Hey? Any sign at all?&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8220;No. Maybe if I had been faster.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other EMT was talking to Tim&amp;#8217;s wife. Tim peaked, allowing one eye to slowly nlid. He could make them out, standing right in front of the doors. They weren&amp;#8217;t look at him. She was standing there, arms folded across her chest, face ashen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8221;I&amp;#8217;m sorry, Mrs. Keller, we just don&amp;#8217;t know. The folks up at St. Mary&amp;#8217;s will be able to tell you more.&amp;#8221; The EMT put his hand on her shoulder. &amp;#8220;We&amp;#8217;ve got to go now.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She nodded, eyes tight. She was making that face, that universal face of someone who doesn&amp;#8217;t trust themselves to speak.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This has gone too far. Just sit up, and tell everyone you&amp;#8217;re fine.&lt;/em&gt; Tim thought.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But he might have to explain that he was fine, there was nothing wrong with him, and he had just been really embarrassed and had wanted to pretend he was anywhere but here. However, Tim decided he couldn&amp;#8217;t look the EMT in the eye if that happened, so he kept his eyes closed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-&amp;gt;*&amp;lt;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8220;He just isn&amp;#8217;t responding. We still don&amp;#8217;t even know what&amp;#8217;s wrong with him. Okay look,&amp;#8221; The doctor turned his monitor around, bringing up two videos and gesturing at them with his pen. &amp;#8220;These are two MRI&amp;#8217;s. One is a healthy person, cogent and awake, the other is your husband.&amp;#8221; The doctor looked up at Tim&amp;#8217;s wife, &amp;#8220;Can you tell which is which?&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tim&amp;#8217;s wife was fidgeting with a tissue, her face pinched. &amp;#8220;Well, no. But I&amp;#8217;m not a doctor!&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The doctor leaned back in his chair and raised his hands up. &amp;#8220;Trust me, no one can. We&amp;#8217;re flying the best neurologist in the country here. He should be here tomorrow.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ghost of a wince crept over Tim&amp;#8217;s face.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The doctor stood up, and began to pace. &amp;#8220;Mrs. Keller, Tim&amp;#8217;s brain will actually respond to stimuli. If you speak to him, the speech centers of the brain light up, as if he is thinking of a response. He just can&amp;#8217;t seem to translate that into control over his body. Yet his spine is just fine!&amp;#8221; The doctor threw his hands in the air, fixing Tim&amp;#8217;s wife with a pleading look. &amp;#8220;You don&amp;#8217;t understand how frustrating this is, Mrs. Keller. We think that this is the only way.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8220;You said he is fine. You said he is in there. Why do you want to cut him open?&amp;#8221; Tim&amp;#8217;s wife started to cry. &amp;#8220;Why won&amp;#8217;t he wake up?&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The doctor sat, not looking at her. Tim&amp;#8217;s wife stood up, softly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8221;I&amp;#8217;m sorry. Do whatever you think is best, Doctor. Even if that means&amp;#8230;&amp;#8221;, she paused, dabbing at her eyes with the tissue. &amp;#8220;Even if that means the surgery you described.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The doctor nodded. &amp;#8221;I&amp;#8217;m sorry, Mrs. Kelley. We&amp;#8217;re doing the best we can, we really are.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She nodded once, slowly, before she left. The doctor followed her out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This had gone on far too long. It is out of control.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He couldn&amp;#8217;t even bear to think about how much money this was costing his insurance company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I&amp;#8217;ll just tell them I feel fine, and I would like to go home.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tim walked himself through the scenario, imagining the hollow pronouncement&amp;#8211;&amp;#8220;Hey guys. Miracle! I feel fine now.&amp;#8221;, the slight suspicion in his wife&amp;#8217;s eyes, the knowing look the doctor would give him, that you-little-fucker-you&amp;#8217;ve-been-fine-this-whole-time-and-we-flew-down-the-best-neurologist-in-the-country-who-do-you-think-you-are look.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No, that would be simply too much. It would be too much to face everyone now. Tim decided he would just have to wait it out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#8217;m sorry. I&amp;#8217;m so sorry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-&amp;gt;***&amp;lt;-&lt;/p&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>First Princess Day</title>
   <link href="http://aboottown.com/2015/11/25/First-Princess-Day/"/>
   <updated>2015-11-25T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://aboottown.com/2015/11/25/First-Princess-Day</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h1 id='the_first_princess_day_or_how_i_learned_that_mexican_amateur_porn_involving_bicycles_is_just_better'&gt;The First Princess Day: or How I Learned that Mexican Amateur Porn Involving Bicycles is Just Better&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sitting here, eating a fresh egg-salad&lt;sup id='fnref:1'&gt;&lt;a href='#fn:1' rel='footnote'&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; with corn chips and sipping some tequila, I am comforted by the comfortable distance of a few days between the writing of this post, and the actual events being recorded. I had several visceral physical reactions to my first princess day outing, and they left me questioning many things&lt;sup id='fnref:2'&gt;&lt;a href='#fn:2' rel='footnote'&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, our story begins much earlier where, flush from the triumphant baptism of a new day&lt;sup id='fnref:3'&gt;&lt;a href='#fn:3' rel='footnote'&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;, I and several other friends decided to inaugurate princess day. After considering the listings of events in Boulder, I found one that seemed quirky, original, and obscure enough to mark one as a man who had his finger on the pulse of the city. Perfect date material, even if the date is oneself. This is how I decided on Bike Smut! A Film Festival dedicated to exploring the intersection of mobility and sexuality&lt;sup id='fnref:4'&gt;&lt;a href='#fn:4' rel='footnote'&gt;4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. This would then be followed by One Dollar Tacos at Mountain Sun. A one-two combination sure to dazzle anyone! Tacos, then tacos&lt;sup id='fnref:5'&gt;&lt;a href='#fn:5' rel='footnote'&gt;5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plus, as an avowed Star Trek, Star Wars and all around science fiction fan, the added cherry on top was that this year the theme was Science Friction. All this was to turn to ash in my mouth. The eating-tacos at the Mountain Sun were nice though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id='the_festival'&gt;The Festival.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, a disclaimer. Please read the below as one man trying to put you in his, admittedly purityrannical, reaction to these films. My comments are not meant to be body-shaming &lt;sup id='fnref:6'&gt;&lt;a href='#fn:6' rel='footnote'&gt;6&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; in anyway&amp;#8211; I am merely trying to describe the intense reactions that I felt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mexican Lesbians. They kiss, one goes riding, one starts masturbating. Commentary on the solo, fetishized &amp;#8216;movement-for-movement&amp;#8217;s-sake&amp;#8217; philosophy of recreational cycling? Perhaps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Charlie Chaplin. Begins in black and white. Homeless man gifts sex toy to woman. She uses it (offscreen&lt;sup id='fnref:7'&gt;&lt;a href='#fn:7' rel='footnote'&gt;7&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;), and the world becomes full of vibrant colours.&lt;sup id='fnref:8'&gt;&lt;a href='#fn:8' rel='footnote'&gt;8&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hispanic woman masturbates while straddling bicycle in a park. Most &amp;#8216;arty&amp;#8217; of the films. I enjoyed this for its tasteful restraint. By using metaphorical imagery (notably, an engorged red balloon inflating), and accompanied by a dulcimer that discordantly hammered away, the audience was induced into an anxious, uncomfortable, but aroused state. Presumably the same state that would lead a Mexican to masturbate on a bike in a park.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shitty &amp;#8216;arty&amp;#8217; film&amp;#8211;German Neo Expressionism taken so seriously it becomes parody. Derivative.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Note. At this point, I had begun pulling from a flask that I had secreted on my person, and things start to become a little hazy.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;?. Domestic mystery, detective noire. Bikes are sentient. One enlists the aid of a hardboiled detective to unravel domestic affair. Detective peaks in on couple having sex while standing over a bike. Note: this is the first real &amp;#8216;porn&amp;#8217;, in the sex scene has no artistic merit and is just two people fucking with bad sound production. And lots of hair.&lt;sup id='fnref:9'&gt;&lt;a href='#fn:9' rel='footnote'&gt;9&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;?+1. Post-apocalyptic. Woman tracks down man, brainwashes him into having sex with her&lt;sup id='fnref:10'&gt;&lt;a href='#fn:10' rel='footnote'&gt;10&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; First close up of a dick and cum-on-titties-shot. Dick has an interesting geometry. Also, I realized that when men walk with hard dicks it looks like Jim Hennison is controlling it somewhere offscreen, giving it an alien rythmn as it bobs and weaves. This film was silent, and better for it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;?+2. Bike sleeps around. Best filmed straight-up porn scene. Good lighting, music was suitable. Also Mexican&amp;#8211; no surprise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;?+3. Post-apocalyptic with heavy handed morality segues into weird glitter sex with &amp;#8216;Rubenesque&amp;#8217; girl.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;?+4. Animated. (Also, no surprise, Mexican.) Artistic, fun. Highlight of the festival.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;?+5. &amp;#8216;Classic&amp;#8217; style porn with two sex scenes. One where a drugged man is anally penetrated with a strapon. Again, I am triggered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By far the worst of the night was a prolonged skit where one of the presenters dressed up like Picard, and then fought Khan, to the music where Kirk fights Spock when Spock has succumbed to the anicient Vulcan mating drive known as Pon Farr in the &amp;#8220;Amok Time&amp;#8221; espisode of the Orginal Series. It hurt to watch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then Darth Vader entered the scene and while I didn&amp;#8217;t gag this time, I felt an intense feeling of disgust. Not merely content to rape drugged up black dudes, the Bike Smut festival had now violated some of the most sacred science fiction icons of our time. I was greatly disappointed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, we left, and went to get tacos. And we thought about what just happened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id='closing_thoughts'&gt;Closing thoughts.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Somewhere in there was a film that caused a physical reaction from me. Two lesbians, one young, one old, have sex in a bike shop. The older one is hoisted up, so she is suspended in mid-air. A Macgyvered sex-toy in the form of a screwdriver whose shaft had been driven into a drill, and all covered with a condom is brought up to her vagina.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, something about the combination of a moist, hairy, and meaty&lt;sup id='fnref:11'&gt;&lt;a href='#fn:11' rel='footnote'&gt;11&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; vagina being perturbed by a screwdriver handle moving at 100 rpm made me gag. Seeing the vagina undulate like the Baron Harkonnen smacking his lips, hearing the tinny whine of the power drill, seeing the light glisten off her labia like roast beef under the buffet heat lamps, and the almost surgical dispassion of the young woman operating the drill, it all combined to produce a sensory experience that was overwhelming to me, and I gagged. Repeatedly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am still coming to terms with: a) my reaction to that, and b) what that says about me. Have I been so indoctrinated by media and well-produced porn to only find hairless (or tasteful landing stripped), vaginas whose cup does not overflowth with meat, attractive?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes. I suppose so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fucking patriarchy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the words of Supreme Court Justice Potter when asked how to distinguish good porn from bad porn&amp;#8211; &amp;#8220;I know it when I see it&amp;#8221;, and unfortunately, that night I didn&amp;#8217;t see any.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class='footnotes'&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li id='fn:1'&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Soooo fucking fresh&lt;sup id='fnref:12'&gt;&lt;a href='#fn:12' rel='footnote'&gt;12&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href='#fnref:1' rev='footnote'&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id='fn:2'&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vaginas? Hair? Naturalness: Is it Beautiful?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href='#fnref:2' rev='footnote'&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id='fn:3'&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Frequent readers of my blog will know that it gives me pleasure to baptise a new day, ie. Bitch Day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href='#fnref:3' rev='footnote'&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id='fn:4'&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, a refreshing &amp;#8216;sex-positive but also winky innuendo&amp;#8217; vibe that would be sure to score points with a woman who belongs in 2015.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href='#fnref:4' rev='footnote'&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id='fn:5'&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#8217;m sorry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href='#fnref:5' rev='footnote'&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id='fn:6'&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although, where do you drawn the line? No one is telling people with inflamed buttholes to be proud of them. There are no butthole movement on twitter where people post pictures of their buttholes and are congratulated on having a beautiful butthole. But, hairy, meaty vaginas are something to be embraced. I&amp;#8217;m sorry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href='#fnref:6' rev='footnote'&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id='fn:7'&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A rare display of tastefulness from a porn festival.&lt;sup id='fnref:13'&gt;&lt;a href='#fn:13' rel='footnote'&gt;13&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href='#fnref:7' rev='footnote'&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id='fn:8'&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, the reversal of this film technique was used to similarly stunning fashion with the Girl in The Red Coat in Schindler&amp;#8217;s List.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href='#fnref:8' rev='footnote'&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id='fn:9'&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am pro-GMO, and as such, reject the conflation of Naturalness and Beauty. If Michael Jordan shaves his armpits, so can you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href='#fnref:9' rev='footnote'&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id='fn:10'&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gone were my illusions of consent-positivity&lt;sup id='fnref:14'&gt;&lt;a href='#fn:14' rel='footnote'&gt;14&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; in this festival of pornographers. Frequent readers of my blog will suspect that it is here I began to be triggered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href='#fnref:10' rev='footnote'&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id='fn:11'&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like an Arby&amp;#8217;s commercial.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href='#fnref:11' rev='footnote'&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id='fn:12'&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The small, unintended pleasures of bachelor living.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href='#fnref:12' rev='footnote'&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id='fn:13'&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Make no mistake, at this point all notions of a Tasteful Burlesque Show of innuendo and sex-positivity were gone. I was watching pornography. With friends. In a bar. And the sound production was terrible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href='#fnref:13' rev='footnote'&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id='fn:14'&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although, it does raise interesting questions of consent. How would I have felt if the genders were reversed? (even ickier) If it happened over the course of a week and she just manipulated (was charming) him into having sex with her would I feel icky then? (no).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href='#fnref:14' rev='footnote'&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Princess Day</title>
   <link href="http://aboottown.com/2015/11/24/Princess-Day/"/>
   <updated>2015-11-24T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://aboottown.com/2015/11/24/Princess-Day</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Princess day was born out of my frustration with the courtship process. I found that I was spending money, time and energy planning and executing first, second and third dates for complete strangers. Unfortunately, the patriarchy won&amp;#8217;t let women plan and execute their own dates and this asymmetry had started to bother me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Especially with the statistic fact that 50% of the people you meet are going to be &lt;a href='https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Statistics'&gt;shitheads&lt;/a&gt;, this can all add up to heartbreak and dissatisfaction. Thus, Princess Day was born of the simple realization that, instead of treating these complete strangers as princesses to be pampered and feted, I should be treating myself that way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, Princess Day is a date that I take myself, and any close friends who want to come, on. Because, at the end of the day, you are the most important person, so let yourself know that.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Introducing Aboottown</title>
   <link href="http://aboottown.com/2015/11/23/Introducing-aboottown/"/>
   <updated>2015-11-23T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://aboottown.com/2015/11/23/Introducing-aboottown</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h1 id='introduction'&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This blog is for personal use only. Please stop reading immediatly. Its purpose is to record the goings on of a young, single man in Boulder, Colorado.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I created this blog by using this helpful young man&amp;#8217;s &lt;a href='http://joshualande.com/jekyll-github-pages-poole/'&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
