<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Aboot Town</title>
 <link href="http://aboottown.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://aboottown.com/"/>
 <updated>2015-11-23T12:47:06-07:00</updated>
 <id>http://aboottown.com</id>
 <author>
   <name>Adam Wooster</name>
   <email>adamblog@gmail.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Princess Day</title>
   <link href="http://aboottown.com/2015/11/24/Princess-Day/"/>
   <updated>2015-11-24T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://aboottown.com/2015/11/24/Princess-Day</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Princess day was born out of my frustration with the courtship process. I found that I was spending money, time and energy planning and executing first, second and third dates for complete strangers. Unfortunately, the patriarchy won&amp;#8217;t let women plan and execute their own dates and this asymmetry had started to bother me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Especially with the statistic fact that 50% of the people you meet are going to be &lt;a href='https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Statistics'&gt;shitheads&lt;/a&gt;, this can all add up to heartbreak and dissatisfaction. Thus, Princess Day was born of the simple realization that, instead of treating these complete strangers as princesses to be pampered and feted, I should be treating myself that way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, Princess Day is a date that I take myself, and any close friends who want to come, on. Because, at the end of the day, you are the most important person, so let yourself know that.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Introducing Aboottown</title>
   <link href="http://aboottown.com/2015/11/23/Introducing-aboottown/"/>
   <updated>2015-11-23T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://aboottown.com/2015/11/23/Introducing-aboottown</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h1 id='introduction'&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This blog is for personal use only. Please stop reading immediatly. Its purpose is to record the goings on of a young, single man in Boulder, Colorado.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I created this blog by using this helpful young man&amp;#8217;s &lt;a href='http://joshualande.com/jekyll-github-pages-poole/'&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
